<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kaoru Negisa on More than Men</title>
    <link>https://chaos46692.github.io/author/kaoru-negisa/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Kaoru Negisa on More than Men</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 09:00:25 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chaos46692.github.io/author/kaoru-negisa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>I Cant Believe We Have to Cover This Again</title>
      <link>https://chaos46692.github.io/posts/00552_i-cant-believe-we-have-to-cover-this-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 09:00:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chaos46692.github.io/posts/00552_i-cant-believe-we-have-to-cover-this-again/</guid>
      <description>(missing image)
 The most insidious form of douchebag is the Misunderstood Douchebag. You know the type: he&amp;rsquo;s really not that bad, people just don&amp;rsquo;t understand his ways. If only people got that what he was doing was noble and not at all in the blind pursuit of getting into girls&#39; pants, the world would be a much fairer place. The Misunderstood Douchebag is the genus of the species Nice GuyTM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Its Not Going to Work How to Argue with Privilege</title>
      <link>https://chaos46692.github.io/posts/00434_its-not-going-to-work-how-to-argue-with-privilege/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2012 09:00:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chaos46692.github.io/posts/00434_its-not-going-to-work-how-to-argue-with-privilege/</guid>
      <description>By now, everybody in the atheosphere is familiar with the Jessica Ahlquist story, and especially the latest development&amp;amp; in the saga. The sheer amount of bigotry, hatred, and blind, unthinking idiocy on display by citizens of Cranston is astonishing, made no less so by their calls for religious tolerance.
&amp;hellip;wait for it&amp;hellip;.
&amp;ldquo;Religious tolerance?!&amp;rdquo;
(missing image)  That&amp;rsquo;s right, kids. We&amp;rsquo;re being the intolerant ones. Most of you are familiar with this trick where no distinction is made between &amp;ldquo;public&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;private,&amp;rdquo; and where reality is blown so far out of proportion that if I didn&amp;rsquo;t know the facts of the case, I&amp;rsquo;d be outraged, too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kaoru I Really Thought This was Satire</title>
      <link>https://chaos46692.github.io/posts/00408_kaoru-i-really-thought-this-was-satire/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2012 09:00:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chaos46692.github.io/posts/00408_kaoru-i-really-thought-this-was-satire/</guid>
      <description>Want to thank the people at More Than Men for having me. To start, I&amp;rsquo;d like to share a recent post from my own blog, then I&amp;rsquo;ll get to work on some original content. Enjoy!
You know, I had other things to do. Better things to do. I really, really wanted to stop being a complete asshole and actually answer my email, because I love my friends and I have been an irresponsible ass about that.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
